killermovies.com 2002-12-08

# Privacy Policy for KillerMovies.com

**Privacy Statement for KillerMovies.com**  

**KillerMovies.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for **KillerMovies.com**

**Information Automatically Logged**  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.  
Your IP address will not be used for any other purpose.

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use Gorilla Nation, DoubleClick and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). 

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party ad server, Gorilla Nation, Double Click or their affiliates, or individual advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

**Personal Information**  
This Web site may request information from you to use certein features of the site, such as mailing list and the forums.  
We do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any other purposes. 

**Public Forums**  
This site makes forums/message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Stats**  
We use Webtrends Live to analyze traffic to this web site. WebTrends Live does not create individual profiles for visitors. Unlike some tracking services WebTrends Live does not have a database of individual profiles for each visitor. WebTrends Live only collects aggregate data. For more information about WebTrends Live privacy policy, please click [here](http://www.webtrendslive.com/privacy_policy.htm). 

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [staff@killermovies.com](mailto:staff@killermovies.com)
